Subhan Nizar Fullstack Engineer

+6281353995458

Mataram, Nusa Tenggara Barat, Indonesia

in subhan-nizar-15a027131

? ganggas95

PROFILE

Middle-level Fullstack Engineer with +6 years of experience working with local companies and International Companies. Creating test cases, creating Rest-API based on JSON data schema, and fast learning. And strong ability to write reusable, clean, and refactoring old code to be more readable code. Fluent in Python, NodeJs, Typescript, and Javascript Framework and Javascript Library such as Vue.js and React.js.

SKILLS

Vue3 and Vue.js • React.js • Typescript

Javascript • Apollo GraphQL • Python

Flask (Create an RestAPI) • SQLAlchemy

Docker • Golang • NodeJS • HTML & CSS

Angular • Next.JS • Nuxt.js • Git

Tailwind • Unocss • Bootstrap • Vite

Nginx • Redis • Celery • PostgresSQL

MySQL • NodeJs

NestJS (Create an RestAPI)

LANGUAGES

Bahasa Indonesia

English



PROFESSIONAL EXPERIENCE

Quokka HR, Fullstack Engineer
2021 – present | Wan Chai, Hongkong Island
Quokka is a Software-as-a-Service (SaaS)
employee engagement platform that develops
engaged & high-performing teams. I helped
this company for 2 years to develop and
maintain the main platform based on the Frontend side. Refactor the base code from Vue.js to
Vue3 and make the code cleaner.

ITEC Mataram, Fullstack Engineer ☑ 2016 – 2021 | Mataram, Indonesia ITEC Mataram is a software house that handles several projects in West Nusa Tenggara Government. And also a course institution located in the city of Mataram that provides various kinds of course programs. Here I'm a mentor, handling several projects and building its own POS(Point of Sales) project.

Lombok CyberLab, Junior Full Stack Engineer 2016 – 2017 | Mataram, Indonesia

COURSES

Server Side Rendering using React and Redux, Udemy ☑

EDUCATION

Hamzanwadi University,

D3 Management Information 2013 – 2016 | Selong, Indonesia

PROJECTS

QuokkaHR People Management,

SaaS People Management 🛮

October 2021 – present

Skills: Vue.js, Vite, Nuxt.js, Python, Flask,

Apollo GraphQL, SQLAlchemy

Sitampan Kota Bima, Employee Government

Management System And Attendance

Management System 🛮

November 2018 – October 2021

Skills: Python, Flask, Fast API, Vue.js,

SQLAlchemy, Celery, Redis, PostgresSQL.

Landa POS, Point of Sales Platform by ITEC

June 2018 - November 2020

Skills: Python, Flask, SQLAlchemy, React.js,

Next.js

GIS BWS NT1, Geographic Information

System of Area River at West Nusa

Tenggara 🗷

January 2017 – June 2017

Skills: Python, Flask, SQLAlchemy, jQuery,

Javascript, Google Maps API